dogheirs.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy - DogHeirs

Last Updated May 24, 2018

We want to earn your trust by being transparent about how DogHeirs works.

Our privacy policy explains how we treat your personal data and protect your privacy when you use our Services. By accessing our website, you agree to our privacy policy and terms of use. The information contained on DogHeirs.com is for informational purposes only.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which DiscoverMe Technologies, Inc. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://www.dogheirs.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services (“Services”) offered by DiscoverMe Technologies, Inc. (“DiscoverMe”).

**Questions.** If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, contact our team:  **hello**   **(@) dogheirs.com**

**No information from children under age 13.** If you are under age 13, please do not attempt to register for DogHeirs or provide any personal information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under age 13, please contact us:  **hello**   **(@) dogheirs.com**

**Parental participation.** We strongly recommend that minors 13 years of age or older ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet and we encourage parents to teach their children about safe internet use practices. 

When visiting DogHeirs.com, we collect no personally identifiable data about you as a visitor. The only exception is when you provide 1) your email address to subscribe to our electronic newsletter, which you can opt out of at any time, 2) register to become a member and may provide your name, email address to “Make a Post” and, 3) make a purchase and provide your name and address via our shop only.

We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters and payment processing. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes of advertising. Our advertisers may use cookies to serve you better ads (see “Advertising” below). 

Note: DiscoverMe Technologies works with partners and third-party providers who are both “Controllers” and “Processors” under the GDPR. Details of their GDPR compliance can be found on their individual privacy policies.

**Personal information.**

**Newsletter:** When you sign up for the DogHeirs newsletter you provide your e-mail address, which you can opt out of at any time by selecting the “Unsubscribe” link included at the bottom of every email. If you have any difficulty you can contact us directly. Please note that once we receive your request, it may take an additional period of time for your opt-out to become effective.

**Member Sign Up:** When you sign up for DogHeirs as a Member and to “Make a Post” you provide us with your name, email. During the registration process we give you the opportunity to provide additional profile information. In some cases we may ask for additional information for security reasons or to provide specific services to you. 

We store personal data of members who join our website’s member services. Information stored includes: username, name (if provided), email address, thumbnail image if provided.

Anyone signing up through the email registration is sent a verification email to authenticate and opt-in to this service. You can modify your profile visibility, change your email, or delete your account by selecting “Settings” available when you log in. Deletions of account can also be made upon request by emailing: hello (at) dogheirs.com.

Users who login to our site using their social networking information (for example Facebook, Twitter or G+) maintain all privacy and control of their account through these third-party technology providers. In the case that Users use their social networking information, the authentication of your login credentials are conducted through that third party social networking service. When you link your social networking accounts with our Site or engage with our Site through third party social media platforms, we may have access to certain of your information stored on those social networking media services depending upon the service and your privacy settings. In addition, as you interact with our Site, the social networking service may collect information about your activities on our Site. We recommend you review the information your third party social networking services may make available to us by visiting those services’ privacy policies and/or modifying your privacy settings directly with those services. We reserve the right to use, transfer, assign, sell, share and provide access to all information that we receive through these third party social media services in the same ways described in this Privacy Policy. You agree that we shall not be liable for the use by social networking services of any information. 

**Content.** One of the reasons people sign up for DogHeirs is to share content with others, such as uploading a photo, sharing a link, writing a blog post, sharing a video, upvoting, downvoting, asking a question and answering questions. If you do not want us to store metadata associated with content you share on DogHeirs (such as photos), please remove the metadata before uploading the content.

**Payment Information.**  
We may provide paid products and/or services within the Site. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processor we work with is PayPal. Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at: <https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>.

## Device and Browser Information

When you access DogHeirs.com from a computer, mobile phone, or other device, we may collect information from that device about your browser type, location, and IP address, as well as the pages you visit on our Site using Google Analytics. This information is collected anonymously and is accessed through and stored by Google.

  * Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
  * You can opt-out of having made your activity on our Site available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. To learn about Google Analytics’ currently available opt-outs for the Web, please visit: <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881?hl=en>.
  * For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

## Advertising

We may use third-party Service Providers to show advertisements to you to help support and maintain our Site. Third-party Service Providers we select include:

  * Google AdSense: Google Adsense, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Site. You may control the information Google uses to show you ads through Google by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page: [http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)  
Note: Using the Google Ads Settings, visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads.
  * Taboola: Taboola, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Site. Taboola’s use of the cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Site or other websites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the Taboola Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the Taboola page: <https://www.taboola.com/cookie-policy>
  * Amazon: Amazon, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Site. To learn more about Amazon and their use of cookies visit Amazon’s Privacy Policy page: <https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496>

**Cookie Information**  
We may use “cookies” (small pieces of data we store for an extended period of time on your computer, mobile phone, or other device) to make DogHeirs.com easier to use.

Examples of cookies we use on our Site:

  * Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
  * Advertising Cookies. Advertising Cookies are used to serve you with advertisements that may be relevant to you and your interests.

We allow third-party companies, such as Google and Taboola (see “Advertising”), to collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website through cookies. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.

These companies typically use a cookie or a third party web beacon to collect this information. For example, we use Google Analytics to support our Display Advertising and collect non-personally identifiable information about our visitors’ demographics and interests.

Some of our third party partners (including advertisers and marketing services companies) may set and access Cookies on your computer as well. We do not have control over how these third parties use such cookies and similar technologies or the information derived therefrom, and this Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that such third parties may have collected from you or the methods used by the third-parties to collect that information.

**Networking Advertising Initiative:** Some of the advertising service providers may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies. If you opt-out of receiving targeted ads in this manner, you will continue to receive advertising messages after you opt-out, but they will not be customized to you based on your use of the Websites and/or third party websites.

To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org or visit ](https://www.networkadvertising.org/)<http://www.aboutads.info/> for more information. You can also remove or block cookies using the settings in your web browser, but in some cases this action may impact your ability to use DogHeirs.

The collection of information via certain ads served to users in Canada may be managed by visiting [youradchoices.ca](http://youradchoices.ca/).

**Do Not Track: We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”)**. Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

Please note that the-opt out is cookie-based and will only affect the specific computer and browser on which the opt-out is applied.

## How We Use Your Information:

We use the information we collect to try to provide a safe, efficient, and customized experience. Here are some of the details on how we do that:

**To manage the service.** We use the information we collect to provide our services and features to you, to measure and improve those services and features, and to provide you with customer support. We use the information to prevent potentially illegal activities, and to enforce our Terms of Service. For example, we use a variety of technological systems to detect and address anomalous activity and screen content to prevent abuse such as spam. These efforts may on occasion result in a temporary or permanent suspension or termination of some functions for some users.

**To contact you.** We may contact you with service-related announcements from time to time.

## How We Share Information:

**DogHeirs is about sharing information with others.** We share your information with third parties when we believe the sharing is permitted by you, reasonably necessary to offer our services, or when legally required to do so. For example: 

**To help improve or promote our service.** Sometimes we share aggregated anonymous analytics information with third parties to help improve or promote our service. But we only do so in such a way that no individual user can be identified or linked to any specific action or information.

**To provide you with services.** We may provide information to service providers that help us bring you the services we offer. For example, we may use third parties to help host our website, send out email updates about DogHeirs, remove repetitive information from our user lists, process payments, or provide search results or links (including sponsored links). These service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time, but when this occurs we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections to limit their use of that information to helping us provide the service.

**To respond to legal requests and prevent harm.** We may disclose information pursuant to subpoenas, court orders, or other requests (including criminal and civil matters) if we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law. This may include respecting requests from jurisdictions outside of Canada where we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law under the local laws in that jurisdiction, apply to users from that jurisdiction, and are consistent with generally accepted international standards. We may also share information when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activity, to prevent imminent bodily harm, or to protect ourselves and you from people violating our Terms of Service. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, courts or other government entities.

**Transfer in the Event of Sale or Change of Control.** If the ownership of all or substantially all of our business changes, we may transfer your information to the new owner so that the service can continue to operate. In such a case, your information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

## How You Can View, Change, or Remove Information:

**Viewing and editing your profile.** You may change or delete your profile information at any time by going to your profile page and clicking “Account Details.” Information will be updated immediately.

**Deleting your account.** If you want to stop using your account you may delete it. When you delete an account, it is permanently deleted. You should only delete your account if you are certain you never want to reactivate it.

**Limitations on removal.** Even after you remove information from your profile or delete your account, copies of that information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been shared with others, or it was copied or stored by other users.

**Backup copies.** Removed and deleted information may persist in backup copies for up to 90 days, but will not be available to others.

**Unsubscribing to Newsletter.** If you wish to stop receiving our newsletter you may unsubscribe at any time by clicking on the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of every email.

Note: Upon personal request we can provide users with the personal data export or erasure requests. 

**Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**  
If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), DiscoverMe Technologies’ legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.

DiscoverMe may process your Personal Data because:

– You have given us permission to do so  
– The processing is in our legitimate interests and it’s not overridden by your rights  
– For payment processing purposes  
– To comply with the law

**How We Protect Information:** We do our best to keep your information secure, but we need your help.

**Risks inherent in sharing information.** Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you share your information. We cannot guarantee that only authorized persons will view your information. We cannot ensure that information you share on DogHeirs will not become publicly available. We are not responsible for third party circumvention of any security measures on DogHeirs. You can reduce these risks by using common sense security practices such as choosing a strong password, using different passwords for different services, and using up to date antivirus software. 

**Report Violations.** You should report any security violations to us at  **hello**   **(@) dogheirs.com**

**Links To Other Sites:** Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

**Changes to the DogHeirs Privacy Policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy without notice. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy we will notify you by publication here.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy please [contact us](https://www.dogheirs.com/contact/).
